<resources>
    <string-array name="bio_data_array">
        <item>Lavender, a fragrant flowering plant native to the Mediterranean region, is celebrated for its soothing aroma and versatile uses. Its calming properties make it a popular choice in aromatherapy, while its subtle flavor enhances both sweet and savory dishes. Lavender is also valued for its antiseptic qualities, making it a common ingredient in skincare products and home remedies.</item>
        <item>Turmeric, scientifically known as Curcuma longa, is a flowering plant belonging to the ginger family, Zingiberaceae. Native to South Asia, turmeric is cultivated primarily for its rhizomes, which are dried and ground to produce the vibrant yellow-orange spice commonly used in curry powders, sauces, and traditional medicine. Curcumin, the active compound in turmeric, is renowned for its potent anti-inflammatory and antioxidant properties. Turmeric has been used for centuries in Ayurvedic and traditional Chinese medicine to alleviate various ailments, including arthritis, digestive disorders, and skin conditions. In recent years, turmeric has gained widespread popularity for its potential health benefits, leading to the development of turmeric supplements and extracts. Turmeric's earthy flavor and vibrant color make it a versatile ingredient in both savory and sweet dishes, while its medicinal properties continue to be studied for their potential therapeutic applications.</item>
        <item>Rosemary, scientifically known as Rosmarinus officinalis, is an aromatic evergreen shrub native to the Mediterranean region. Belonging to the Lamiaceae family, rosemary is prized for its fragrant needle-like leaves and delicate blue flowers. This versatile herb has a long history of culinary and medicinal use, dating back to ancient civilizations such as the Greeks and Romans. Rosemary is celebrated for its rich, pine-like flavor, which complements a wide range of savory dishes, from roasted meats to soups and stews. Beyond its culinary applications, rosemary is esteemed for its potential health benefits. It's believed to possess antioxidant and anti-inflammatory properties, and it's often used in herbal medicine to support memory, improve digestion, and promote hair and scalp health. Rosemary essential oil is also utilized in aromatherapy for its invigorating aroma and stimulating effects on mental clarity and focus.</item>
        <item>Ginger, botanically known as Zingiber officinale, is a flowering plant native to Southeast Asia and valued for its pungent rhizome, which is used as both a spice and a medicinal herb. Belonging to the Zingiberaceae family, ginger has a long history of use in various cuisines and traditional medicine systems, including Ayurveda and Traditional Chinese Medicine. The rhizome of the ginger plant contains bioactive compounds such as gingerol, which exhibit potent anti-inflammatory, antioxidant, and digestive properties. Ginger is commonly consumed fresh, dried, or as a powder, adding a warm, spicy flavor to dishes, beverages, and confections. It's renowned for its ability to alleviate nausea, aid digestion, reduce muscle soreness, and relieve menstrual discomfort. Ginger tea, made from fresh ginger slices steeped in hot water, is a popular remedy for colds, flu, and upset stomachs.</item>
        <item>Chamomile, derived from the Asteraceae family, encompasses several species of daisy-like flowering plants, including German chamomile (Matricaria chamomilla) and Roman chamomile (Chamaemelum nobile). These aromatic herbs are native to Europe, Western Asia, and North Africa and have been valued for their gentle, calming effects for centuries. Chamomile is commonly consumed as a tea, cherished for its delicate floral flavor and potential health benefits. It's renowned for its soothing properties, which can help promote relaxation, relieve stress, and improve sleep quality. Chamomile tea is also believed to aid digestion, reduce inflammation, and soothe gastrointestinal discomfort. Additionally, chamomile is used topically in skincare products to calm irritated skin and promote healing.</item>
        <item>Peppermint, a hybrid of watermint and spearmint, is a perennial herbaceous plant prized for its cooling menthol flavor and myriad health benefits. Belonging to the Lamiaceae family, peppermint is native to Europe and the Middle East but is now cultivated worldwide. The leaves of the peppermint plant contain volatile oils, primarily menthol, which impart its characteristic taste and aroma. Peppermint has a long history of use in traditional medicine for its digestive, respiratory, and analgesic properties. It's often consumed as a tea or used topically to alleviate symptoms such as indigestion, nausea, headaches, and muscle pain. Peppermint essential oil is also utilized in aromatherapy to enhance focus, alleviate tension, and promote a sense of invigoration.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name = "plant1">lavender</string>
    <string name = "plant2">turmeric</string>
    <string name = "plant3">rosemary</string>
    <string name = "plant4">ginger</string>
    <string name = "plant5">chamomile</string>
    <string name = "plant6">peppermint</string>
    <string name="todo">todo</string>
    <string name="plant">Plant</string>
    <string name="click_me">click_me</string>
</resources>